Tam Nguyen

Undergraduate Researcher at the University of Kentucky

Computer Science student with 4+ years of experience in C++, 2 years of experience in Python, Javascript, and HTML, some experience in Qt. Seeking to utilize creative problemsolving skills in a software development or UX position.

Experience

2018-08 - Undergraduate Researcher

present

University of Kentucky, Digital Restoration Initiative

- Digitally unroll Ancient Greek and Biblical-era scrolls for modern reading
- Develop 3D Computer Vision, 3D to 2D Image Processing pipeline
- Present research in Paris to promote international scholarship
- Design UI with Qt Creator

2019-06 - Software Development Intern

2019-08

Spectrum

- Develop analytics tool for Spectrum modems across 46 states in Javascript and HTML
- Build UI to automate error reporting

2018-05 - Student Software Developer

2018-10

University of Kentucky

- Build smoother web UI
- Maintain SQL database

2018-06 -

Software Development Intern

2018-08

Abt Associates

- Develop website in PHP and Javascript from user requirements with SQL database design
- Implement JIRA and Agile development principles to build user story

Education

2016-08 -

University of Kentucky, Computer Science Major,

Mathematics Minor

- GPA: 3.79
- Awards: National Merit Scholar, Patterson Scholar, Duke Energy Scholar
- Coursework: Web Programming, Graphics & Multimedia, Machine Learning, Databases, Artificial Intelligence, Web Crawling, Algorithms, Data Structures

Projects

2019-05 Presented research

at Columbia University's Reid Hall in Paris, France

2019 Awarded 1st Place

at Kentucky Academy of Science Research Presentation

2019-04 Built web-crawler

to analyze Youtube's Recommended algorithm

Personal Info

Phone

(704) 724-6153

E-mail

tam.k.nguyen14@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/tamKN

Languages

Python

Javascript

C++

HTML

Skills and Frameworks

Qt Creator

Agile Development

JIRA Product Management

Microsoft Office (Word, Powerpoint, Excel, etc.)

Linux, Unix

Windows

MacOS